Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1819 -- 2009; UA136.002; 4.6 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1412 Digital Object(s)
  - Bray Laboratory, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01762; Tufts Camera Club (Box Shared 112)
    Laboratories; photographic print
  - Bromfield Pearson Building, June 5, 1924; UA136.002.DO.01763; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Bromfield-Pearson Building, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01764; Unknown (Box Shared 114)
  - Robinson Hall, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01765; Unknown (Box Shared 114)
    Robinson Hall; photographic print
  - Anderson Hall, 1961; UA136.002.DO.01766; Duette (Box Shared 114)
  - Bookstore, 1954; UA136.002.DO.01767; Duette (Box Shared 115)
    Buildings; People; photographic print; Bookstore
  - View of Tufts Grounds, UA136.002.DO.01768; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Corner of Capen and Winthrop St, Feb. 13, 1897; UA136.002.DO.01769; Velox (Box Shared 112)
  - Winter outside Braker Hall, 1956; UA136.002.DO.01770; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Grounds of Tufts, College Hill, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01771; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - View of academic quad, 1886; UA136.002.DO.01772; Hardy (Box Shared 115)
  - Pansy Farm, College Ave., 1890; UA136.002.DO.01773; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Goddard Chapel, UA136.002.DO.01774; Curran, Donald (Box Shared 115)
  - Goddard Chapel, UA136.002.DO.01775; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01776; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Building and Grounds, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01777; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - P.T. Barnum's Famous "Jumbo", 1900; UA136.002.DO.01778; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - East Hall, Ballou, Packard, and West, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01779; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Grounds, 1875; UA136.002.DO.01780; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Artist Rendering of Grounds, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01781; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Jumbo, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01782; Pastorello, Richard (Box Shared 112)
  - Ballou Hall, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01783; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Alexander Bain Society Picnic, May 18, 1941; UA136.002.DO.01784; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    Oversize; Scan cropped from Original
    photographic print; Mead, Leonard Chapin
  - Alexander Bain Society Picnic, May 18, 1941; UA136.002.DO.01785; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    photographic print; Kennedy, John L.; Wessell, Nils Yngve
  - Alexander Bain Society Picnic, May 18, 1941; UA136.002.DO.01786; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve
  - Chester P. Earle, 1916; UA136.002.DO.01788; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    photographic print; Earle, Chester P.
  - Commencement 1941 [Deans], UA136.002.DO.01800; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard
  - Commencement 1941 [Deans], UA136.002.DO.01801; Shearer Photography (Box Shared 115)
  - Faculty of Tufts College, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01802; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Faculty having their picture taken at Commencement, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01803; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Faculty of Arts and Sciences
  - George S. Miller and Vannevar Bush, 1930; UA136.002.DO.01804; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; photographic print; Miller, George Stewart; Bush, Vannevar
  - Tufts Faculty under President Capen, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01805; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Faculty, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01806; Duette (Box Shared 115)
  - President's Cabinet; February 17, 1959. Standing: Prof. Paul H. Flint, Dean Joseph Hayman, dean Clifton W. Emery, Dean Robert B. Stewart, Dean Benjamin B. Hersey. Sitting: Dean Cyril D. Marshall-Day, Dean Richard A. Kelley, Dean Katherine R. Jeffers, Vice President and Provost Leonard C. Mead, President Nils Y. Wessell, Vice President for Development Frank A. Trendinnick, Jr., UA136.002.DO.01808; Duette (Box Shared 115)
    photographic print; Flint, Paul H.; Hayman, Joseph M.; Emery, Clifton W.; Stewart, Robert B.; Hersey, Benjamin B.; Marshall-Day, Cyril D.; Kelley, Richard A.; Jeffers, Katherine Rosetta; Mead, Leonard Chapin; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Tredinnick, Frank A., Jr.
  - Ballou Hall, UA136.002.DO.01809; Duette (Box Shared 115)
  - Administration Deans, UA136.002.DO.01811; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Leadership Workshop; October 7, 1967; UA136.002.DO.01812; Duette (Box Shared 115)
    People; College presidents; photographic print; Maloney, Dean; Hallowell, Burton Crosby
  - Schmidt, Alvin R., UA136.002.DO.01813; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    Students; People; Faculty; photographic print; Schmidt, Alvin Jr.
  - Schmidt, Alvin, 1955; UA136.002.DO.01814; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
    People; photographic print; Schmidt, Alvin Jr.
  - Schmidt, Alvin, 1955; UA136.002.DO.01815; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Schmidt, Alvin [dancing], 1955; UA136.002.DO.01816; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Ballou Hall, 1884; UA136.002.DO.01818; Unknown (Box Shared 115)
  - Alexander Jackson, Janitor, 1910; UA136.002.DO.01822; Horner Photography (Box Shared 112)
    People; photographic print; Jackson, Alexander
  - Gertie Claus, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01823; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    People; photographic print; Claus, Gertie
  - Sarah W. MacAdam, 1951; UA136.002.DO.01829; Duette (Box Shared 116)
    Press Release Included
    People; photographic print; MacAdam, Sarah W.
  - Allen Clemon and Betty Curtin at Alumni Day, 1980; UA136.002.DO.01834; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
    photographic print; Clemon, Allen; Curtin, Betty
  - The Bursar, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01837; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - World War I, Physical Education, Captain Bowman, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01838; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
    photographic print; Bowman, Captain
  - World War I, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01839; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Rapid Bridge Construction, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01840; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Rapid Bridge Construction, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01841; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Jackson Women forming for Armistice Parade, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01842; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - SATC Band, World War I, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01843; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Somerville Police Detail for Armistice Parade, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01844; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Gathering for Armistice Day Parade, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01845; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Moving the Bleachers, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01846; Unknown (Box Shared 112)
  - Ensign McCutcheon, Commander of Naval Unit, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01847; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; McCutcheon, Ensign
  - Sergeant Thorne "Blackie", 1915; UA136.002.DO.01848; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Thorn, "Blackie"
  - Naval Unit Inspection, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01849; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Inspection Co.C., 1915; UA136.002.DO.01850; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - How the boys looked after the uniforms arrived, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01851; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Top floor of Bromfield Pearson, also used as shop, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01852; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Instructors in Carpentry and Auto Mechanics, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01853; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Naval Unit Inspection, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01854; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Laboratory, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01855; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - First New Hampshire and Vermont Boys in front of West Hall, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01856; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - The Convict Army - before uniforms arrived, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01857; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - War Gardens, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01858; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Power House Extension complete with automobiles under repair, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01859; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Intensive Civil Engineering, Prof. Conner director, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01860; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Tufts Wireless Club and their exhibit, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01861; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, Soldier in Uniform, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01862; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Service Flag, World War I., 1915; UA136.002.DO.01863; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, Goddard Chapel, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01864; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01865; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Power house Extension complete with automobiles under repair, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01866; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, 1915; UA136.002.DO.01867; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
  - World War I, Eaton Hall, ca. 1914-1918., UA136.002.DO.01868; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - World War I, Faculty Representation, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01869; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
  - Marching to Barracks from class work, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01870; Unknown (Box Shared 116)
  - Falling in after dinner, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01905; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Naval Unit falls in, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01906; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - NROTC class in front of Cousens Gym, 1946; UA136.002.DO.01912 (Box Shared 28)
    Reserve Officers Training Corps (Navy); Navy V-12 Program; photographic print
  - Student Body Photo, 1955; UA136.002.DO.01915; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Students in a tree, 1910; UA136.002.DO.01917; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Image of Two Girls in a dorm, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01918; Duette (Box Shared 28)
  - Student body photo, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01920; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Student Body, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01921; Duette (Box Shared 28)
  - Student Body, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01922; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Student outside Ballou, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01923; Duette (Box Shared 28)
  - Student Body Photograph, 1975; UA136.002.DO.01924; Siteman, Frank (Box Shared 30)
  - Students in Cousens Gym taking Final Exams, 1975; UA136.002.DO.01925; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Barnum Hall, UA136.002.DO.01959; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall from Goddard Chapel, 1923; UA136.002.DO.01960; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; photographic print
  - Provost's House, Christmas Eve, 1921; UA136.002.DO.01962; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    photographic print; McCollester, Lee Sullivan
  - From College Hill looking toward Somerville; Capen House, Ballou, and corner of Schneider House, 1883; UA136.002.DO.01963; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
    Houses; photographic print
  - Tweed House and Shipman House, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01964; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Professor Marshall's House, 48 Professors Row, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01965; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01966; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Original Bell on Ballou, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01967; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Original campus wall along the row, 1858; UA136.002.DO.01968; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    3x4
  - Ballou Hall, 1892; UA136.002.DO.01969; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Ballou Hall and Goddard Chapel, 1883; UA136.002.DO.01970; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
    Buildings; Chapels; photographic print
  - Ballou from Professor's Row, 1882; UA136.002.DO.01971; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Path to Ballou Hall, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01972; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Ballou Hall and Chapel Tower, 1930; UA136.002.DO.01973; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Capen House, 1964; UA136.002.DO.01975; Duette (Box Shared 30)
  - Ballou Hall, before lawn was grated to street level, 1874; UA136.002.DO.01976; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, Bowen Porch: June 15, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01977; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Western view of Ballou Hall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.01982; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Ballou from the north side, from class of 1879 photo album., 1878; UA136.002.DO.01983; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Path to Ballou Hall, 1945; UA136.002.DO.01984; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou hall from northern view, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01986; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01988; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Capen House, 1950; UA136.002.DO.01989; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
    Houses; Dormitories; photographic print
  - Students standing at the top of Memorial Steps in front of the Fischer Arcade, 1954; UA136.002.DO.02008; Duette (Box Shared 30)
    People; Students; Monuments; photographic print
  - All-Around Club Faculty Tea, Fall, 1957; UA136.002.DO.02009; Duette (Box Shared 30)
    People; Events; Faculty Tea; photographic print; All Around Club
  - All Around Club, November 23, 1948; UA136.002.DO.02010; Duette (Box Shared 30)
    People; photographic print; Harrington, Jean; Volante, Joyce; Dudley, Jane; MacArthur, Ruth; All Around Club
  - All Around Club, 1947; UA136.002.DO.02011; Duette (Box Shared 30)
    People; photographic print; All Around Club
  - Chapel and Ballou Hall, 1884; UA136.002.DO.02012; Folsom, A.H. (Box Shared 30)
    Buildings; Chapels; Academic; Administrative; photographic print
  - Memorial Steps, UA136.002.DO.02014; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Eaton Library from Miner Hall, UA136.002.DO.02016; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Miner Hall, 1892; UA136.002.DO.02017; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Prof. Dearborn's Room, 1893; UA136.002.DO.02018; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Brown House, site of Campus Center, Professors Row, UA136.002.DO.02019; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - College Building now Ballou Hall, 1872; UA136.002.DO.02020; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Student Body, 1970; UA136.002.DO.02021; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 30)
  - University Store, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02022; Morrow Christopher W. (Box Shared 30)
  - Student Body, 1961; UA136.002.DO.02023; Duette (Box Shared 30)
  - View from the hill of President's house and Boston in the distance, 1880; UA136.002.DO.02024; Unknown (Box Shared 30)
  - Mrs. Robert. S. Swain, 1940; UA136.002.DO.02032; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - Ballou Hall, mowing the campus with a horse and carriage, 1890; UA136.002.DO.02034; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
  - The library in Packard Hall, 1880; UA136.002.DO.02035; Unknown (Box Shared 28)
    Buildings; Libraries; photographic print
  - A. A. Eliot resignation party, 1952; UA136.002.DO.02080; Unknown (Box Shared 31)
    Child Development; photographic print; Eliot, Abigail A.
  - The Spree Club with Lee Maulsby as leader, 1876; UA136.002.DO.02183; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Misc."
    People; Clubs; copy negative; Maulsby, Lee; Spree Club
  - View southeast from Ballou, 1875; UA136.002.DO.02190; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Views"
    Views; copy negative
  - Professor John P. Marshall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.02238; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts People"
    Faculty; copy negative; Marshall, John P.
  - Charles P. Stevens, 1884; UA136.002.DO.02498; Hardy (Box Shared 29)
    People; Student activities; photographic print; Stevens, Charles P.
  - Charles P. Stevens, 1884; UA136.002.DO.02499; Hardy (Box Shared 29)
    People; Students; photographic print; Stevens, Charles P.
  - Professor of Engineering Charles Durlin Bray, 1894; UA136.002.DO.02500; Hearn (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Bray, Charles Durlin; Dept. of Civil Engineering; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1870; UA136.002.DO.02501; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1892; UA136.002.DO.02502; Horner Photography (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1870; UA136.002.DO.02503; Hardy (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1891; UA136.002.DO.02504; Davis and Dow (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1890; UA136.002.DO.02505; Hastings (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1887; UA136.002.DO.02506; Ritz (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1875; UA136.002.DO.02507; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1875; UA136.002.DO.02508; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Charles Bray, 1870; UA136.002.DO.02509; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
  - Elias Day, June 22, 1884; UA136.002.DO.02510; Hardy (Box Shared 29)
    Faculty; Students; photographic print; Day, Elias E.
  - Elias E. Day, 1884; UA136.002.DO.02511; Hardy (Box Shared 29)
    People; Students; photographic print; Day, Elias E.
  - Eaton Library, 1908; UA136.002.DO.02512; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    Buildings; Libraries; photographic print; Library
  - Dr. Louis J.P. Calisti, Dean of Tufts Dental School, 1962; UA136.002.DO.02545; Lenscraft Photos, INC. (Box Shared 32)
    People; Deans; photographic print; Calisti, Louis J.P.
  - Dean Louis Calisti and President Burton Crosby Hallowell breaking ground for construction of the School of Dental Medicine, 1969; UA136.002.DO.02546; Duette (Box Shared 32)
    People; Deans; Administrative; photographic print; Calisti, Louis J.P.; Hallowell, Burton Crosby
  - Dr. Louis J.P. Calisti, Dean of Tufts Dental School, 1962; UA136.002.DO.02547; Lenscraft Photos, INC. (Box Shared 29)
    People; Deans; copy negative; Calisti, Louis J.P.
  - Tufts professor Dr. Vannevar Bush, E'1913, G'1913, H'1932, 1933; UA136.002.DO.02604; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar; Dept. of Mathematics; Dept. of Physics; College of Engineering
  - Dr. Vannevar Bush on the cover of Popular Mechanics Magazines, October, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02605; Unknown (Box Shared 55)
    8x11
  - Dr. Vannevar Bush, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02606; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Frank H. Lahey, 1927; UA136.002.DO.02607; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Lahey, Dr. Frank H.; Dept. of Medicine
  - Professor Robert L. Nichols, February 9, 1940; UA136.002.DO.02634; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Dept. of Geology
  - Professor of Dramatics Marston Balch, 1980; UA136.002.DO.02635; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Dept. of Drama
  - Dr. Max Tishler, A'28, Tufts "most illustrious chemistry student" and trustee, 1967; UA136.002.DO.02636; Duette (Box Shared 29)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Tishler, Max; Board of Trustees
  - Trustee and Tufts graduate Dr. Max Tishler, A'28, 1967; UA136.002.DO.02637; Duette (Box Shared 29)
  - Robert Nichols, Tufts' Henry Bromfield Pearson Professor of Natural Sciences, 1985; UA136.002.DO.02638; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Marston Balch, 1960; UA136.002.DO.02639; Duette (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor Marston Balch, 1980; UA136.002.DO.02640; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
  - Professor of Robert Nichols, 1960; UA136.002.DO.02641; Duette (Box Shared 29)
  - Chemist Max Tishler, A'28, 1982; UA136.002.DO.02642; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
    photograph included in the Summer 1982 issue of the Criterion on pg. 23
  - Dr. Max Tishler, 1965; UA136.002.DO.02643; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Max Tishler, receiving an honorary Doctorate of Science from Rider College, January 18, 1970; UA136.002.DO.02644; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Max Tishler, A'28, and his wife, Elizabeth Verveer, J'31, 1982; UA136.002.DO.02645; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Tishler, Elizabeth Muriel; Tishler, Max; Board of Trustees
  - Dr. Max Tishler, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02646; Westfield Studios (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Max Tishler, 1956; UA136.002.DO.02647; Duette (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Max Tishler, 1965; UA136.002.DO.02648; Unknown (Box Shared 32)
  - Dr. Max Tishler receiving an award from two men identified only as Cairno and Chollay, May 2, 1961; UA136.002.DO.02649; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
  - Dr. Max Tishler, Vice President for Scientific Activities of Merck & Co., and President of Merck Sharp & Dohme Research Laboratories, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02650; Westfield Studios (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
  - Professor Marston Stevens with Fletecher Professor Emeritus Kalman Burnim, 1978; UA136.002.DO.02651; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Dept. of Drama; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Sidney Michaels, A'49, Professor Marston Stevens, and New York City Mayor John Lindsay at the Margo Jones Award Presentation, 1966; UA136.002.DO.02652; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; Events; Awards; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Michaels, Sidney; Lindsay, John; Dept. of Drama
  - Dr. Marston Balch addressing a class, 1951; UA136.002.DO.02653; Duette (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Dept. of Drama
  - Dr. Marston Balch delivering the New York Address at the New York Tufts Club Annual Spring Dinner, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02654; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Events; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Dept. of Drama
  - President Jean Mayer with Dr. Marston Balch and Mrs. Balch after his retirement, 1971; UA136.002.DO.02655; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; College presidents; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens; Dept. of Drama; Office of the President
  - Peter Roeder at Black Rock Cairn, 1930; UA136.002.DO.02656; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    People; photographic print; Roeder, Peter
  - Tufts College-National Science Foundation Antarctic Expedition, 1960 -- 1961; UA136.002.DO.02657; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    People; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Borns, Harold W. Jr.; Denton, George H.; Hart, Roger A.; Schempp, Ellory F.; Calkin, Peter E.; Tufts College; National Science Foundation
  - Professor Robert L. Nichols and students, 1963; UA136.002.DO.02658; Wolfe, Richard E. (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Ludden, Lawrence; Dowell, Mary; Biederman, Don; Dept. of Geology
  - Dr. Robert L. Nichols and unidentified student with camping equipment, 1954; UA136.002.DO.02659; Duette (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Dept. of Geology
  - Dr. Robert Nichols with student peeking outside of tent, 1954; UA136.002.DO.02660; Duette (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
  - An unidentified man with Robert L. Nichols upon receiving an honorary Doctorate of Science, 1978; UA136.002.DO.02661; Siteman, Frank (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; Events; Commencement; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Dept. of Geology
  - Professor Robert Nichols speaking with unidentified man, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02662; Duette (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
  - Dr. Robert L. Nichols and Dr. Donald C. Haney looking at Nichols' Miner Award, 1960; UA136.002.DO.02663; Whitlock, Bob (Box data_value_missing_a45a1a0fc7915667a4873cb6176d1fb0)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Haney, Donald C.; Dept. of Geology
  - Front entrance to Eaton Hall, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02664; Unknown (Box Shared 63)
  - Circulation desk in Eaton Library, 1930; UA136.002.DO.02665; Unknown (Box Shared 29)
    Interior views; Libraries; photographic print; Library
  - A view of Eaton Hall, including the War Memorial Library addition, 1950; UA136.002.DO.02666; Unknown (Box Shared 63)
  - President Leonard Carmichael and his daughter Martha work in their family's Victory Garden, 1943; UA136.002.DO.02668; Unknown (Box Shared 63)
    People; College presidents; World War, 1939-1945; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard; Carmichael, Martha; Office of the President
  - Edward J. Shea, Julius Doliner, and President Purton Crosby Hallowell, 1976; UA136.002.DO.02669; Ellis Herwig Photography (Box Shared 63)
    [Shea (L), Doliner (R), and Hallowell (background)]
    People; Alumni and alumnae; College presidents; photographic print; Shea, Edward J.; Doliner, Julius; Hallowell, Burton Crosby; Office of the President; Tufts Alumni Association